<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hopton 10k road and trail running race, Mirfield, West Yorkshire</title>
    <link>https://hopton10k.run/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hopton 10k road and trail running race, Mirfield, West Yorkshire</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hopton10k.run/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning</title>
      <link>https://hopton10k.run/blog/2019/07/08/planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hopton10k.run/blog/2019/07/08/planning/</guid>
      <description>Latest preparations Short Road Closure There way still be three months to go before the Hopton10k but preparations are in full swing. We&amp;rsquo;ve had confirmation that we can temporarily close Calder Road, Granny Lane and Stenard Lane for twenty minutes between 10:00 and 10:20. This will allow the start of the race to be completely car free, I&amp;rsquo;d expect all runners to have entered the woods by 10:15.
Parking We have secured additional parking for around twenty cars at Lower Hopton WMC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking the route</title>
      <link>https://hopton10k.run/blog/2019/07/07/recce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hopton10k.run/blog/2019/07/07/recce/</guid>
      <description>Never take under kids on a 10k walk without snacks! Today I decided it was a &amp;lsquo;good idea&amp;rsquo; to take the whole family out to walk the Hopton 10k route.
It turns out the 10k undulating route feels a lot longer when you&amp;rsquo;re listening to kids complaining about being tired and carrying a toddler for 60% of the time.
However, we made it, and we picked several key areas to place marshals and signage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteers needed</title>
      <link>https://hopton10k.run/blog/2019/06/24/become-a-volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hopton10k.run/blog/2019/06/24/become-a-volunteer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;become-a-volunteer&#34;&gt;Become a volunteer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love getting up early?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://hopton10k.run/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hopton10k.run/contact/</guid>
      <description>Have a question? Don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to get in touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions</title>
      <link>https://hopton10k.run/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hopton10k.run/faq/</guid>
      <description>There will be more FAQs added to this page over the next few months as questions come up.
When is the race? 10 am on Sunday the 6th October 2019. Please try to arrive no later than 20 minutes before the start so you can collect your race number.
How old must I be to enter the Hopton 10k? You must be 15 years of age to enter the Hopton 10k race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship</title>
      <link>https://hopton10k.run/sponsorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hopton10k.run/sponsorship/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in sponsoring the Hopton 10k? We have various packages available, see the options below. To get in touch and discuss the options in more detail please contact us using the form below.
Package 1: Platinum Sponsor (£700) – 1 package available In return for your support as platinum sponsor, Hopton 10k would provide:
 Presenting sponsor i.e. &amp;ldquo;The 2019 Hopton 10k brought to you by (Your Company Name Here)&amp;rdquo; Your company logo in priority position and size on the Hopton 10k T-shirt (awarded to all runners) Your company logo on the Hopton 10k website with a link to your company website A shout out on the Hopton 10k race Facebook page and twitter account with a link to your website Your company logo on the Hopton 10k Start / Finish line banner A space at the event to host a display table / promotional stand (provided by sponsor) Acknowledgement on the day over the race PA system Opportunity to add your branded materials, leaflets or promotional items into the goody bags (at sponsor’s own cost) Consecutive event sponsorship available (you will get first refusal on next year’s event) Primary sponsor mention and thank you in the event recap on website and Facebook 10 x FREE entries to the race.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>